Guide to the Football Game Film Collection, 1934-2007 UA.13.01.0004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Football Game Films
  - North Carolina, 1991 November 23
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 4 Sideline, 1991 November 23; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0149)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: End zone 1, 1991 November 23; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0150)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 2 End zone, 1991 November 23; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0151)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: End Zone 3, 1991 November 23; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0152)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: End Zone 4, 1991 November 23; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0153)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Sideline, 1991 November 23; VHS (Box 37)
      Reference copy.
  - Clemson, 1991 November 30
    Duke loss, score: 21-33
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Tape 1, 1991 November 30; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0154)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Tape 2, 1991 November 30; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0155)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Tape 3, 1991 November 30; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0156)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: All, 1991 November 30; VHS (Box 40)
  - Florida State, 1992 September 05
    Duke loss, score: 21-48
    - Duke vs. Florida State: First Quarter, 1992 September 05; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0157)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Second Quarter, 1992 September 05; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0158)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Third Quarter, 1992 September 05; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0159)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Fourth Quarter, 1992 September 05; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0160)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: 1 Sideline, 1992 September 05; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0161)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: 2 Sideline, 1992 September 05; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0162)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: 3 Sideline, 1992 September 05; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0163)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: 4 Sideline, 1992 September 05; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0164)
  - Vanderbilt, 1992 September 12
    Duke loss, score: 37-42
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: First Quarter, 1992 September 12; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0165)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: Second Quarter, 1992 September 12; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0166)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: Third Quarter, 1992 September 12; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0167)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: Fourth Quarter, 1992 September 12; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0168)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: End zone 1, 1992 September 12; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0169)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: 2 End zone, 1992 September 12; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0170)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: End Zone 3, 1992 September 12; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0171)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: End Zone 4, 1992 September 12; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0172)
  - Rice, 1992 September 19
    - Duke vs. Rice: 1 Sideline, 1992 September 19; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0173)
    - Duke vs. Rice: 2 Sideline, 1992 September 19; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0174)
    - Duke vs. Rice: 3 Sideline, 1992 September 19; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0175)
    - Duke vs. Rice: 4 Sideline, 1992 September 19; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0176)
  - Virginia, 1992 September 26
    Duke loss, score: 28-55
    - Duke vs. Virginia: 1 Sideline, 1992 September 26; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0177)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: 2 Sideline, 1992 September 26; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0178)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: 3 Sideline, 1992 September 26; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0179)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: 4 Sideline, 1992 September 26; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0180)
  - East Carolina, 1992 October 10
    Duke win, score: 45-14
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: End zone 1, 1992 October 10; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0181)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: 2 End zone, 1992 October 10; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0182)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: End Zone 3, 1992 October 10; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0183)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: End Zone 4, 1992 October 10; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0184)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: 1 Sideline, 1992 October 10; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0185)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: 2 Sideline, 1992 October 10; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0186)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: 3 Sideline, 1992 October 10; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0187)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: 4 Sideline, 1992 October 10; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0188)
  - Clemson, 1992 October 17
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 1 Sideline, 1992 October 17; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0189)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 2 Sideline, 1992 October 17; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0190)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 3 Sideline, 1992 October 17; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0191)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 4 Sideline, 1992 October 17; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0192)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: End zone 1, 1992 October 17; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0193)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 2 End zone, 1992 October 17; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0194)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: End Zone 3, 1992 October 17; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0195)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: End Zone 4, 1992 October 17; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0196)
  - Maryland, 1992 October 24
    Duke loss, score: 27-25
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 1 Sideline, 1992 October 24; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0197)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 2 Sideline, 1992 October 24; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0198)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 3 Sideline, 1992 October 24; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0199)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 4 Sideline, 1992 October 24; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0200)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: End zone 1, 1992 October 24; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0201)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 2 End zone, 1992 October 24; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0202)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: End Zone 3, 1992 October 24; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0203)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: End Zone 4, 1992 October 24; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0204)
  - Georgia Tech, 1992 October 31
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 1 Sideline, 1992 October 31; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0205)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 2 Sideline, 1992 October 31; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0206)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 3 Sideline, 1992 October 31; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0207)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 4 Sideline, 1992 October 31; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0208)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: End zone 1, 1992 October 31; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0209)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 2 End zone, 1992 October 31; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0210)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: End Zone 3, 1992 October 31; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0211)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: End Zone 4, 1992 October 31; BetaCamSP (Box 41, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0212)
  - Wake Forest, 1992 November 07
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 1 Sideline, 1992 November 07; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0213)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 2 Sideline, 1992 November 07; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0214)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 3 Sideline, 1992 November 07; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0215)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 4 Sideline, 1992 November 07; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0216)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: End zone 1, 1992 November 07; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0217)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 2 End zone, 1992 November 07; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0218)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: End Zone 3, 1992 November 07; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0219)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: End Zone 4, 1992 November 07; BetaCamSP (Box 42, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0220)
  - NC State, 1992 November 14
    Duke loss, score: 27-45
    - Duke vs. NC State: 1 Sideline, 1992 November 14; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0221)
    - Duke vs. NC State: 2 Sideline, 1992 November 14; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0222)
    - Duke vs. NC State: 3 Sideline, 1992 November 14; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0223)
    - Duke vs. NC State: 4 Sideline, 1992 November 14; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0224)
    - Duke vs. NC State: End zone 1, 1992 November 14; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0225)
    - Duke vs. NC State: 2 End zone, 1992 November 14; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0226)
    - Duke vs. NC State: End Zone 3, 1992 November 14; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0227)
    - Duke vs. NC State: End Zone 4, 1992 November 14; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0228)
  - North Carolina, 1992 November 21
    Duke loss, score: 28-31
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 1 Sideline, 1992 November 21; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0229)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 2 Sideline, 1992 November 21; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0230)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 3 Sideline, 1992 November 21; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0231)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 4 Sideline, 1992 November 21; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0232)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: End zone 1, 1992 November 21; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0233)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 2 End zone, 1992 November 21; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0234)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: End Zone 3, 1992 November 21; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0235)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: End Zone 4, 1992 November 21; BetaCamSP (Box 40, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0236)
  - Florida State, 1993 September 04
    Duke loss, score: 7-45
    - Duke vs. Florida State: 1 Sideline, 1993 September 04; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0237)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: 2 Sideline, 1993 September 04; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0238)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: 3 Sideline, 1993 September 04; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0239)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: 4 Sideline, 1993 September 04; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0240)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: End zone 1, 1993 September 04; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0241)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: 2 End zone, 1993 September 04; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0242)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: End Zone 3, 1993 September 04; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0243)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: End Zone 4, 1993 September 04; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0244)
  - Rutgers, 1993 September 11
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: 1 Sideline, 1993 September 11; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0245)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: 2 Sideline, 1993 September 11; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0246)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: 3 Sideline, 1993 September 11; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0247)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: 4 Sideline, 1993 September 11; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0248)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: End zone 1, 1993 September 11; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0249)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: 2 End zone, 1993 September 11; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0250)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: End Zone 3, 1993 September 11; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0251)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: End Zone 4, 1993 September 11; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0252)
  - Army, 1993 September 18
    Duke win, score: 42-21
    - Duke vs. Army: End zone 1, 1993 September 18; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0253)
    - Duke vs. Army: 2 End zone, 1993 September 18; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0254)
    - Duke vs. Army: End Zone 3, 1993 September 18; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0255)
    - Duke vs. Army: End Zone 4, 1993 September 18; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0256)
    - Duke vs. Army: 1 Sideline, 1993 September 18; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0257)
    - Duke vs. Army: 2 Sideline, 1993 September 18; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0258)
    - Duke vs. Army: 3 Sideline, 1993 September 18; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0259)
    - Duke vs. Army: 4 Sideline, 1993 September 18; BetaCamSP (Box 49, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0260)
  - Virginia, 1993 September 25
    Duke loss, score: 0-35
    - Duke vs. Virginia: End zone 1, 1993 September 25; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0261)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: 2 End zone, 1993 September 25; BetaCamSP (Box 43, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0262)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: End Zone 3, 1993 September 25; BetaCamSP (Box 44, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0263)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: End Zone 4, 1993 September 25; BetaCamSP (Box 44, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0264)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: 1 Sideline, 1993 September 25; BetaCamSP (Box 44, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0265)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: 2 Sideline, 1993 September 25; BetaCamSP (Box 44, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0266)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: 3 Sideline, 1993 September 25; BetaCamSP (Box 44, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0267)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: 4 Sideline, 1993 September 25; BetaCamSP (Box 44, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0268)
  - Tennessee, 1993 October 02
    Duke loss, score: 19-52
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: End zone 1, 1993 October 02; BetaCamSP (Box 44, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0269)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: 2 End zone, 1993 October 02; BetaCamSP (Box 44, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0270)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: End Zone 3, 1993 October 02; BetaCamSP (Box 44, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0271)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: End Zone 4, 1993 October 02; BetaCamSP (Box 44, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0272)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: 1 Sideline, 1993 October 02; BetaCamSP (Box 44, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0273)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: 2 Sideline, 1993 October 02; BetaCamSP (Box 44, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0274)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: 3 Sideline, 1993 October 02; BetaCamSP (Box 44, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0275)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: 4 Sideline, 1993 October 02; BetaCamSP (Box 44, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0276)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unknown game coverage, 1993 October 02; DVD
      Master copy.
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unknown game coverage, 1993 October 02; DVD
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unknown game coverage, 1993 October 02; DVD
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unknown game coverage, 1993 October 02; DVD
- Unprocessed football films, 1993-2007